本字幕由诸神字幕组出品，仅供学习交流，禁止用于商业用途
Morning!
おはよう
更多中日双语字幕，尽在 www.kamigami.org 和微博 @诸神字幕组
つめ切りどうだったの
Did he like the nail clippers?
About that... It was kinda...
それがね
なんかさ…
Morning, Ohta.
おはよう　太田
Yo. Morning, Tanaka.
おはよう　田中
It's cold again today...
今日も寒いね
When it's this cold,
it makes me want to live at school.
こう寒いと　いっそ学校に住みたくなるよ
I'd expect a lazy person to think more
along the lines of "I want to stay at home".
そこは普通　家から出たくなくなるべきなんじゃないか　だるがりとしては
You're oddly conscientious.
変なところ真面目だな
I feel like I should at least attend school every day.
学校くらいはちゃんと来るべきかと思って
Even if my sleepiness wins out
and I fall asleep partway,
たとえ途中で眠気に負けて寝てしまっても
I can claim that I went to the effort of coming.
来る努力はしたんだって主張できる
Thanks.
ありがと
No prob.
Anyway, I'm proud of you for coming.
とにかく　ちゃんと来るのは偉いぞ
To Tanaka-kun
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
眠たい放課後　窓から見下ろす
After school I sit next to a window
春風なびいて　ひと休み
And the spring breeze entices me to sleep
日听
gen & AB
翻译
颜歌＆沐沐
眩しい世界に　片目を瞑れば
So I shut an eye against the dazzling world
日校
小伍
校对
戚风
时轴
WEI&和路雪
压制
wedy96
映し出す景色躍りだす
While the sun makes the scenery dance upon my eyelids
负责人
戚风
頼りない口笛　青空に吹けば
I whistle vaguely at the blue sky
足取りもちょっと軽くなる
And I get more of a spring in my step
騒がしい街角　イヤフォン外して
I remove my earphones in a bustling corner of the city
見上げたら遠く声がする
And look into the distance, where I hear a voice
さぁ陽の光浴びてゆるやかに
Let's bask in the glowing sun
Ever so gently
いつもの今日が始まる
Starting another day as usual
サンシャインと居眠りする
Napping in the sunshine
心地いい場所　君の隣で
In this cozy place with you
優しく胸に響いてる
With all these feelings booming in my heart
字幕
诸神字幕组
Episode 7
Tanaka-kun's Valentine
To Tanaka-kun
Are you giving him chocolate today?
今日さ　先輩にチョコあげるの？
Of course! I made it myself.
もちろん　ちゃんと作ってきたもん
My heart is pounding already!
今からドキドキだよ
What's with that look of utter despair on your face?
なんだ　その絶望を撒き散らされたみたいな顔は
Tanaka, that box... Judging by today's date,
田中　その包みは日付的におそらく
I'm pretty sure it's Valentine's Day chocolate.
というか間違いなくバレンタインチョコだと思うぞ
I know...
わかってる
I don't want to get chocolate on Valentine's Day.
バレンタインチョコとかもらえない方がいい
And if I do, I don't want something
with a strong presence like this,
もらえたとしても　こんな存在感あるのじゃなくて　義理がいい
but an obligatory one.
Must you distance yourself so much from it?
そんな距離を置かなくても…
Why is that?
Don't tell me you don't like chocolate?
なんでだ　もしかしてチョコ嫌いなのか
No, the chocolate's not at fault here.
いや　チョコ自体に罪はない
It's just that I'm not confident I can give
a sincere response if the giver has feelings for me.
ただ　本気チョコに対して真摯な対応をできる自信がまったくないから
It's stressful.
つらい
In fact, I was voted the boy most likely
事実　中学の卒業文集で
to not give anything back on White Day
ホワイトデーにお返しをしてくれなさそうな男子第一位に選ばれた実績が
in my middle school yearbook.
I see...
なるほど　一クラス約３０人分のお墨付きか
Certified by a class of around thirty, huh?
All the more reason you
should redeem yourself here.
なら　なおさらここで汚名返上するべきじゃないか
Heck, I'm jealous you got
a genuine Valentine's Day chocolate.
というか　本気チョコなんて羨ましいぞ
Judging by the box,
it's obviously going to taste good.
包みからして明らかにうまそうだしな
I guess...
そっか
There's one for you too, Ohta.
太田宛てのチョコも入ってる
What?!
なに
To Ohta-kun
Post-It
Chocolate Bar
(98 yen each)
I think we'd both be happier if we traded.
交換した方がお互いに幸せになれそう
No, we shouldn't.
The difference in the amount of love is too great.
いや　やめておこう
想いに格差がありすぎる
It's obviously obligatory chocolate,
but it's better than getting none...
まあ明らかに義理とはいえ　もらえないよりはマシだな
Empty?! Empty?!
ない
な…なぜだ
Why...
Why... isn't there anything in my desk?
なぜ　机になんも入ってない
None... None! Chocolate?
ない　ない　チョコ…
I humbly accept.
ありがたく頂こう
Anyway, who gave you this?
ところで　誰がくれたんだ　これ
Now that you mention it, there's no name...
そういえば　名前書いてないね
Considering this person snuck it into your bag
朝　田中が少し席を外している間に　カバンに忍ばせたと考えると
while you were away from your seat this morning,
it's probably someone from this class.
同じクラスの人っぽいな
True...
確かに
Oh, there's some sort of message on it.
なんかメッセージっぽいのが付いてる
I'm
the
Time
You
watch
ing
All
でね　チョコにおまじないかけたんだ
And then I put a spell on the chocolate.
How romantic!
ロマンチック
Right?
だよね
She must be really shy to not
want me to see her handwriting.
筆跡を極力残さないなんて　よっぽどシャイなのかな
I guess so...
そうだな
I'm sorry, but this is starting
to look more like a crime.
申し訳ないが　少しだけ事件の匂いを感じる
I was so nervous!
緊張した
よく渡したよ　偉い
You gave it to him. I'm impressed! So...
で　何作ったんだ
Girls come in all kinds,
いろんなタイプの女子がいるわけだし
so it'd rude to be suspicious
based on that message alone.
あれくらいで怪しむのも失礼だなぁ
Come to think of it,
there's no doubt that card was handmade.
よく考えてみれば　手作り感溢れるカードだ
I need to make sure Tanaka
gives something in return.
やはり田中にはちゃんとお返しをさせよう
A new chocolatier shop opened
by the station recently,
最近駅前に有名なショコラティエの店がオープンしてたし
so we should look there...
そこで探して…
Honestly, I don't want his response
or anything in return.
正直返事もお返しもいらないよ
I'm too scared...
怖いし
What?!
It's supposed to be three times the value
of the Valentine's gift! Take it, take it!
３倍返しが基本でしょ
もらっとけ　もらっとけ
Really?
そっか
I'd love to get some stylish sweets, then.
じゃあ何かおしゃれなスイーツがいいな
But I'm kinda put off by boys who
know about popular candy stores.
けど　有名店のスイーツとか知ってる男子とか引くわ
I know, right?
わかる
This is hard...
難しいな
The chocolate totally seized, so I panicked.
チョコがさ　まあ見事に分離しちゃってさ
もうほんと焦ったよ
My heart was racing!
マジでドキドキしたって
Hey, Tanaka! This morning...
おーい　田中　今日の朝ってさ
Was it you?
お前か
Huh?
Are you the culprit?
お前が犯人か
Of what?!
なんの…
Tanaka and Katou, what are you two doing?
何してるんだ　田中　加藤
I-I don't know!
Tanaka is saying stuff that doesn't make sense!
わ…わかんない　田中がいきなりわけのわからないことを…
You're not the culprit?
犯人じゃないのか
Sorry.
すまんな　今田中には複雑な事情があってだな
Tanaka is in a complicated
situation at the moment.
Man...
なんだよ
I just wanted to brag about my sign, Sagittarius,
being ranked the luckiest on today's horoscope.
今朝の占い　俺の射手座一位だったの自慢したかっただけなのに
Jeez...
まったくもう
Katou, aren't you a Capricorn
and not a Sagittarius?
加藤　射手座じゃなくて　山羊座じゃないか
Tanaka, I've been thinking...
田中　考えてみたんだが　あのチョコの送り主
Do you think it could be
Miyano who gave you that chocolate?
もしかして宮野じゃないか
It's Valentine's!
バレンタインです
If so, the difference in quality
between yours and mine makes sense.
だとしたら　俺とのチョコ格差も合点がいくぞ
Now that you mention it...
言われてみれば…
The message makes sense too,
since she's watching me all the time.
それにメッセージもしっくりくるね　いつも見られてるし
I see.
そっか　まったく異性として意識してなかったけど
I never saw her as a person of the opposite sex,
but if it's from Miyano-san, I guess it's all right.
宮野さんなら仕方ないか
Bang!
She's more like a "living bullet" to me,
生きる弾丸みたいなイメージだったけど
but I guess she has a sweet side, too.
こんないじらしい一面もあったんだね
I guess so.
そうだな
It seems the path to your becoming
a mature woman is still a steep one, Miyano.
大人の女までの道のりは　まだまだ険しそうだぞ　宮野
I totally forgot to get chocolates
for Master and Ohta-kun!
そういえば師匠と太田くんへのチョコをすっかり忘れてたですー
Seriously? Even though you idolize them?
マジか　あんなに慕ってんのに
I was only thinking about you, Ecchan...
えっちゃんのことしか頭になかったよ
They are boys, so they might've expected
obligatory chocolate, at the least.
あいつらも一応男だし　義理でも期待してたんじゃねぇの
We were 100% wrong...
１００パーセント違うな
Yeah.
It's like, I don't really see them
as people of the opposite sex.
なんというか　あまり異性という認識がなくて
It's more like they exist on the
same plane as God or Buddha!
どっちかというと　神様仏様みたいな世界だから
Even if it was from her,
it would be more like an offering.
もらえてもお供えっぽい物だな
Yeah...
What if...
なんか　もしかしたら嫌がらせだったりして
this was just a prank?
Maybe this person is laughing somewhere,
watching us make fools of ourselves.
こうして翻弄されてる俺たちを見て　陰で笑ってるのかも
I really shouldn't accept this.
やっぱり受け取らない方が…
W-Wait! Don't be hasty, Tanaka!
ま…待て　早まるな　田中
Right, the inside!
そうだ　中身
You should taste it first!
味を見てみよう　味を
She chose this chocolate to be
eaten by the one she loves.
好きな人に食べてほしいと思って選んだチョコだ
I bet you'll feel her love once you try it.
食べてみれば　きっとお前にもその気持ちが伝わるだろう
Oh, in case you don't feel it,
万が一伝わらない場合は　俺が加勢するから安心しろ
I'll help you, so don't worry.
I'll describe her feelings
faithfully on her behalf—
彼女の気持ちを忠実に代弁して…
Yeah.
If he wants some, he should just say so...
食べたいなら食べたいって言えばいいのに
How is it?
どうだ
It's great.
おいしい　ちゃんと愛はあるっぽい
They do seem filled with love.
Really? That's good...
そうか　よかった
So you don't think about getting
a girlfriend or anything like that?
田中は彼女作りたいとか　やっぱり思ったりしないのか
Well, of course the inappropriate curiosity
innate to boys is present in me,
それなりに一般男子並みの不健全な好奇心は持ち合わせてるけど
but not enough that it's worth
the effort to act upon it.
それを満たすために頑張って行動するほどではない
In other words, I'm interested in the erotic,
要するに　エロに興味はあれど
but the process to get there is too much work.
そこへ辿り着くまでのプロセスが超めんどい
There was no need to put it "in other words."
いや　わかりやすく言い直さなくていい
Also, I meant it as a more innocent question.
あと　俺はもっと純粋なレベルの質問をしたつもりだったが
It'd be rude to get closer to a girl
just to satisfy that inappropriate curiosity.
まあ　そういう不健全さだけで女子に近づくのも失礼だし
I believe that when I meet a girl
who makes me want to put in the effort,
いつか俺を頑張らせてくれる人が現れた時
only then can I truly fall in love.
ちゃんとした恋ができるんだと思うよ
I see.
なるほど
Why...
そんな…
Of all things, this is...
よりによってこんな…
What's wrong, Ohta?
どうしたの　太田
It's dark chocolate.
ブラックチョコだ　これ
The kind...
that isn't sweet...
甘くない
Have some of mine.
俺の食べなよ
D-Delicious! I can feel my
wounded heart slowly healing!
うっ　うまい
傷ついた心がどんどん癒えていくのがわかるぞ
I'm glad.
よかった
Hey, now that I look at them...
Aren't these homemade?
というか　よく見てみると　これ手作りじゃないか
What, really?
ほんと？
If so, she's really good at making sweets.
だとしたら相当お菓子作りうまい人だよね
But this sensation...
でもこの感覚　前にもどこかで味わった気がする
I have a feeling I've tasted this before.
So is it store-bought, after all?
となるとやはり市販品なのか
だが俺の脳内スイーツデータベースとの一致が…
But it doesn't match anything
in my brain's sweets database.
I've got it, Tanaka!
わかったぞ　田中
It's Lady Macarons!
マカロンさんだ
Macaron!
マッカロン
誰そのギリシャ神話に出てくる神みたいな人
Who? That sounds like some
goddess from Greek mythology.
A relative of Apollo's?
アポロンの親戚？
S-Sorry. I meant Shiraishi.
す…すまん　白石だ白石
Only Shiraishi can make
something this high-quality.
手作りでこんなクオリティーを出せるのは白石くらいしかいない
She's in our class and she's shy,
despite her looks,
俺たちと同じクラスだし
ああ見えて　内気な性格だから
so she must've snuck it into your bag.
こっそりカバンに入れたんだろう
Shiraishi-san...
白石さん…
I see. Shiraishi-san, huh?
そっか　白石さんか
Now that I know who gave it to me,
I'm starting to feel appreciative.
なんか送り主がわかると　ありがたみ実感できてきた
Good for you, Tanaka.
よかったな　田中
You should set a reminder for
March 14th so you won't forget.
忘れないように　３月１４日リマインダー設定しておけよ
Today is Valentine's?!
今日バレンタイン？
Shiraishi, don't tell me you forgot!
白石まさか　忘れてたの？
I was a loner for so long,
this holiday meant nothing to me...
今までぼっちすぎて縁のないイベントだったから
Huh?
I mean, my mind was preoccupied
with studying for tests...
いや…　テスト勉強で頭いっぱいだったわ
Seriously, who was it?!
誰だ　マジで
The boys must be disappointed.
きっと男子たちがっかりしてるよ
I bet they wanted obligatory chocolate, at least.
義理チョコでも欲しかったんじゃない
But you have someone to give
a true Valentine to, right?
でもあげるなら　本命チョコでしょ
That's right! You said you've
fallen in love with someone.
そうだ　好きな人できたって言ってたじゃん
No, we're not like that yet...
いや
そんな…　まだそういうのじゃ…
そっか
I see.
But if you need someone to talk to, I'll be here.
でも何かあったら相談に乗るからね
We're rooting for you!
応援してるから
Thanks...
ありがとう
The moment I realized
it wasn't from Shiraishi-san,
白石さんじゃないとわかった途端　なんかお腹の調子が…
my stomach started feeling queasy...
The more I think about it,
よく考えたら　このご時世に送り主不明の食品食べるとか
it's dangerous to eat something
given to you by a stranger
in this day and age...
危険すぎるんじゃ…
It can't be that, Tanaka!
そんなことはないはずだ　田中
They tasted so good!
あんなにおいしかったじゃないか
Don't worry.
大丈夫　あのチョコはお前への愛を感じる純粋な味だった
Those chocolates tasted of
someone's pure love for you!
There's nothing disturbing about it at—
不穏なことなんて何一つ…
(Wiretap)
Voice Recorder?
A criminal case...
…事件
C-Calm down, Tanaka!
It's just a misunderstanding!
お…落ち着け　田中　何かの間違いだ
We don't know whether the chocolate
has anything to do with this yet.
まだチョコとこいつが関係あると決まったわけじゃ…
Is something the matter,
どうかしたの
Big Bro?
お兄ちゃん
Master!
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
師匠
It was his sister!
妹です
Tanaka-kun
Is Always
Listless
D-Don't look, Tanaka!
み…見るな　田中　ドッペルゲンガーだ
It's your doppelgänger!
I'm his little sister.
妹です
That's right, you did say
you had a sister in the 9th grade...
そういえば　中３の妹がいるって
Yeah.
I'm his sister, Rino.
妹の莉乃です　兄がいつもお世話になってます
Thank you for always
taking care of my brother.
S-Sorry. I freaked out
because you two look so alike.
す…すまん　あまりにも顔が同じすぎて　取り乱してしまった
Rino, what are you doing here?
莉乃　なんでここに
I needed to go to the supermarket
near your high school.
高校の近くのスーパーに用があって
I see...
そっか
I think I've mentioned him before,
but this is my classmate, Ohta.
前に話したと思うけど　これ　同じクラスの太田
Nice to meet you.
はじめまして
Everything just wears me out so much
俺の体はもう　いろんなことがだるくて
that my body can't survive without Ohta.
太田なしでは生きていけなくなってしまった
That's how important our friendship is.
ってくらい大切な友達
Can't you word that some other way?
もう少し違う言い方できないか　それ
It's misleading...
語弊が…
Anyway, what were you yelling about?
ところで何を騒いでいたの
She ignored that?
流された…
You're not going to comment
on what he said, little sister?
ノーツッコミか　妹
Actually, we found a wiretap
of some sort in Tanaka's bag...
ああいや実は　田中のカバンから盗聴器らしき物が出てきてな
This. It's frightening.
これ　物騒
Oh, that's mine.
ああ　それ私の
I thought I lost it, but I guess
it got mixed up in your things.
ないと思ったら　お兄ちゃんのところに紛れていたんだ
I use this to record my teacher's lectures,
since he talks too fast.
早口で聞き取りにくい先生の授業で使ってるんです
I see. That's convenient
when you need to review later.
なるほど　後で復習する時便利そうだな
No...
いえ
My plan is to make him listen to it so he'll
be aware of his mistakes and correct them.
先生に聞かせて早口を自覚　矯正させるのが目的です
It's to point out his mistakes?!
ダメ出し用…
Brother, why don't you invite your friend
to stop by for tea if he has time?
お兄ちゃん　せっかくだし
もし時間があれば　家でお茶でも飲んでいってもらったら？
May I?
えっ　いいのか
Good idea.
いいね
家の場所　把握してもらえたら
If you know where I live,
you can carry me home from now on.
今度から家まで抱えて連れて帰ってもらえるし
Come over.
おいでよ
I'd prefer to be invited
for a better reason than that.
もうちょっと純粋な動機で招待されたいぞ　俺は
It's decided, then.
じゃあ　決まり
Let's all walk home, Otter-san.
一緒に家に行きましょう
Otter
フトタさん
It's Ohta. You put so much effort into that mistake.
オオタだ
すごく頑張って間違えたな
I'm sorry. I'm not good at remembering names.
ごめんなさい　人の名前覚えるの苦手で
No, I actually enjoyed it.
いや　なかなか楽しませてもらったぞ
I never had anyone make that mistake before.
人生初だ　あんな間違いされたの
You're very positive.
ポジティブなんですね
Tanaka-kun Is Always Listless
Please, go ahead.
どうぞ
Excuse me—
お邪魔しま…
I had to leave this morning before
I could finish cleaning the leather shoes,
今朝ちょっと革靴の手入れをやりかけで出てきちゃったもので
so it's a bit messy.
散らかってますが
No worries.
いや
Will I be able to rescue my own shoes when I leave?
帰る時　俺は無事自分の靴を救出できるんだろうか
I didn't know we had so many leather shoes.
うち　こんなに革靴あったんだ
You're still in middle school,
but you're already taking proper care of shoes.
しかし　中学生で革の手入れをきちんとしているなんて
You're very responsible.
しっかりしているな
Good girl, Rino.
莉乃　偉い
They'll last longer if you take care of them.
ちゃんと手をかければ長く使えますしね
Have some coffee.
コーヒーをどうぞ
Thanks. Sorry to ask,
but could I have some milk and sugar?
おお　ありがとう
すまないが　ミルクと砂糖を…
This coffee tastes best when you take it black.
このコーヒー　ブラックで飲むのが一番おいしいんです
Please drink it as it is.
ぜひブラックで
Is it good? It's good, isn't it?
おいしいですか
おいしいでしょう
Yeah...
A man who usually puts
3 packets of sugar in
It's bitter.
苦い
Their faces look the same,
but his sister is very diligent.
顔は兄と同じだが　性格は至って真面目だな　妹
Still...
しかし　あんなに盛大にだらけていて怒られないのか　田中は
Doesn't she ever yell at him
for being so gloriously lazy?
Rino, I'm here...
莉乃　俺いる
あ　ごめん
Oh, sorry.
I see... She's already given up on him.
ああ　もう諦められてるのか
Udder-san, are you always
with my brother at school?
太ったさんは学校ではいつも兄と一緒なんですか
Hang on!
待て
That doesn't sound remotely
like "Ohta" anymore!
それはもはや　太田の原形をとどめてないぞ
I'm sorry.
すみません
This is the first time my
brother's had a friend over.
兄の友人がうちに来るなんて初めてのことだし
I've heard about you,
太田さんのことは話に聞いていたけど
but I'm nervous now that
I'm meeting you in person.
いざ対面すると緊張してしまって
No, don't worry about it.
いや　いいんだ
I understand.
そうだったのか
She might have secretly worried about
her brother showing no sign of having friends.
今まで友達の気配のない兄のことを密かに心配していたのかもな
She may seem dismissive, but she's probably
a kind sister who cares deeply for her brother.
素っ気なく見えるが　実は兄思いの優しい妹なのかもしれん
I should make sure she knows
安心してもらうためにも
I'm good friends with Tanaka,
so I can offer her reassurance.
田中と仲がいいということをきちんと伝えておこう
Tanaka and I are good friends.
田中には仲良くしてもらってるぞ
We hang out together
pretty much all day at school.
学校ではほとんど一日中一緒だな
I make sure he eats lunch
when he's too lazy to eat.
昼飯食わない時はちゃんと食わせるように気をつけているし
Ahh
I carry him to school
when he's about to be late,
遅刻しそうな時は抱えて運んでやったり
and I go shopping with him after school.
放課後　一緒に買い物に行ったり
I see.
そうですか
Then, starting tomorrow,
please don't do any of that.
じゃ明日から　それら一切やめてください
Leave him alone.
一人にしてください　兄のためにならないので
It's not helping him.
Huh?
Oh, your cup is empty. Care for some more?
コーヒー空ですね　おかわりいります？
No, I've had enough...
いや　もう…
Don't be shy.
どうぞ　どうぞ
いえ　ほんとに…
No, I really don't...
The chocolates I got today would go well with coffee.
今日もらったこのチョコ　コーヒーに合いそう
That's right! I forgot about the chocolates.
おお　そうだ
そういえばチョコがあったな
They'll definitely go well with coffee.
確かにこれは絶対コーヒーと相性がいいぞ
Right, right?
でしょでしょ
Big Bro, you got Valentine's Day chocolate?
お兄ちゃん　バレンタインチョコもらったんだ
Yeah... But I found it in my bag,
so it wasn't really given to me.
もらったっていうか　カバンに入ってた
I don't even know who it's from.
誰がくれたのかもわかんないし
It's very suspicious,
怪しいといえば怪しいが
but we decided there's no malicious intent,
since they tasted good.
味がうまかったから　悪意はないと判断した
Anyone who can make tasty sweets can't be bad.
うまい菓子職人に悪いやつはいない
See? They seem to be homemade.
ほらこれ　なんか手作りっぽいんだけどね
They were very good.
すごくおいしかったよ
I see.
そう
Huh? "Tasty"?
うまかったって
Did Ohta-san eat the chocolate, too?
太田さんもそのチョコ食べたの？
Yeah.
Ohta loves sweets,
太田　甘いもの好きなのに
but he got dark chocolate of all things,
so I gave him some of mine.
よりによってブラックチョコもらっちゃったから　分けてあげた
I see.
…そう
Well, he gave me one,
but it tasted so much better than I expected.
いや　一粒もらったんだが　想像以上にうまくてな
I ended up eating more than half of them.
最終的に半分以上食ってしまった
Hey Ohta, go step outside why don'tcha?
おい太田ちょっと表出ろ
Outside? Is there something outside?
表？　外に何かあるのか
Uh, no... The sun is setting,
いえ
日没ですし　暗くなると危ないので
so I thought you might want to
go home soon, before it gets dark.
そろそろ帰られた方がいいかと
Let's see, which ones are mine?
ええっと　どれだ俺の靴
Here they are.
おお　あった
I'll walk him to the station.
駅まで送ってくる
Okay.
Thanks for having me.
邪魔したな
If you don't mind, I'd love to visit again.
よかったらまた遊びに来させてくれ
Oh, and the coffee was good. See you.
あっ　コーヒーうまかったぞ
じゃあな
It wasn't good at all.
まずかったくせに
I did it on purpose because he likes sweets.
甘党ってわかってたからわざとだもん
I gave him dark chocolate to be mean.
ブラックチョコだって嫌がらせだし
I invited him here because I wanted
to know about my brother's high school life,
お兄ちゃんの学校生活のこと知りたくて家に呼んだけど
but all he did was brag about
how close he is to him!
結局仲良し自慢されるし
How infuriating.
むかつく
No one is closer to my brother than me.
お兄ちゃんと一番仲がいいのは私だもん
I won't let Ohta have him.
太田になんか渡さないんだからね
Do you remember the way to my place?
家までの道覚えた？
I won't be your taxi unless it's an emergency.
緊急時以外のタクシーはやらんぞ
Ohta, I figured it out.
太田　俺わかっちゃったんだけど
It was Rino who gave me the chocolate.
チョコをくれたの莉乃だよ
Seriously?!
マジか
She probably gave you chocolate too,
since you're always taking care of me.
たぶん俺が世話になってるから　一応太田にもくれたんだろうし
To Ohta-kun
It was the wrong choice, though...
ミスチョイスだったけど
Besides, the homemade
chocolates she gave me were...
それに俺宛ての手作りチョコ　あれは…
leftovers from the batch she made for
the boy she likes, and a sample for me to taste.
別の本命宛ての残り物　兼　毒味用
I finished those chocolates
after researching various flavors
あれはお兄ちゃんが好きそうな味を何種類か研究して
my brother might like,
through repeated trial and error!
何回も試作して　ようやく完成したチョコなのに
I worked hard on the wrapping, too,
ラッピングも頑張って
but I'd be embarrassed if he knew it was from me,
でも私からだってわかったら恥ずかしいから
so I made a card he'd never figure out...
カードはわからないように作って
So why did Ohta end up eating them?!
なのに　なんで太田が食べてるのよ
She looked relieved when she saw my reaction.
俺の反応を見て安心してたし
Big brothers are perfect guinea pigs.
身近な実験台には持ってこいだよね　兄って
I see... That's very true!
なるほど　確かに
My sister sometimes gives me
homemade sweets to try
うちの妹もたまに作ったお菓子を最初に持ってきて
to get my opinion.
俺の意見を聞くなぁ
If it has your seal of approval,
it's a guaranteed success.
太田の太鼓判だったら　絶対だもんね
But those chocolates were good, too.
だがあのチョコもうまかった
With that flavor, I'm sure the
boy she likes felt her love.
あの味ならきっと　本命にも妹の想いは届いているはずだ
Yeah. I'm glad...
そだね　よかった
Oh, yeah...
そういえば…
The voice recorder...
ボイスレコーダー
Putting this in the wrong bag
really was an honest mistake,
これは本当にただ間違えてカバンに入っちゃってただけなんだけど
but could it have recorded
my brother's voice at school?
もしかして　学校でのお兄ちゃんの様子が…
Tanaka, that box... Judging by today's date,
田中　その包みは日付的におそらく
I'm pretty sure it's Valentine's Day chocolate.
というか間違いなくバレンタインチョコだと思うぞ
Must you distance yourself so much from it?
そんな距離を置かなくても…
Why is that?
Don't tell me you don't like chocolate?
なんでだ　もしかしてチョコ嫌いなのか
I can only hear Ohta's voice!
Ohta makes me so mad!
太田の声しか聞こえない
太田　むかつく
Everyday life is like a bothersome cat
BON-BON　いつもの　いたずら猫みたい
How I wish I could ignore it and do as I please
自然体で　ワガママしたい
気ままミュージック　こっそりノリノリで
I discreetly retreat into my own world of music
空想なら得意かも
Maybe I have a talent for daydreaming
いわゆる幸せ　それってなぁに？
That so-called happiness
What exactly is it?
I tried acting on my own desires
好きなこと　とことん　やってみて
わかるのかなぁ
Will I understand it now?
BON-BON　ドラマチック
Dramatic listlessness
「そこそこ」が希望
I want to put my life into its hands
ポジティブチケット　持ってたいね
Maybe a positive attitude is better
精一杯なら　正解なのかな
Is trying my best the right thing to do?
ポーカーフェイスは苦手です
I can't hold a poker face
グルグルしちゃうね
Everyday life makes me dizzy
BON-BON　KUBBIDYU
My dear listlessness
もう一回
Once more
BON-BON　KUBBIDYU
My dear listlessness
Tanaka-kun isn't here!
田中くんがいない
おーい　太田が怪我してるぞ
Hey, Ohta's hurt!
If it were me, I could reach Myaano's house
even if no one told me where it was!
あたしなら　教えられなくてもみゃーのんち辿り着けっぞ
That's a get-well gift from Ecchan!
それ　えっちゃんからのお見舞いなんですよ
Well, due to various circumstances, it's gone.
いや　諸事情があって
Next time, Episode 8:
Next Episode
Ohta
次回　第８話「太田くんの受難」
Ohta-kun's Ordeal.